<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PyLadies Grand Rapids</title>
    <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on PyLadies Grand Rapids</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Aug 2017 21:38:52 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/about/</guid>
      <description>PyLadies Grand Rapids We are a group of developers who love the Python programming language. We write code by day or night. Some of us hack on Python projects on the side, while others work with it full-time. Some are just starting out in programming, while others have years of experience.
But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter.
We all just like writing Python code, and that&amp;rsquo;s what brings us together.
Goals  Organize events that facilitate professional development of our members Inspire more people from under-represented groups to fall in love with programming &amp;amp; support and mentor them on their journey Build a revolving community: students become mentors Create a safe, non-threatening environment in the local tech communities  Connect Want to connect?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyLadies hosts Django Girls Grand Rapids 2019 Workshop</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/2019-05-15-djangogirls-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/2019-05-15-djangogirls-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Numbers We hosted our third Django Girls workshop on April 12th - 13th at The Source.
 34 attendees 11 sponsors 12 coaches 5 organizers a ton of supportive friends = An Awesome Workshop  Coffee, Code, Repeat Because our workshop from the previous years were such a success we did a lot of the same things for this year. You can read more about that here.
Pita House catered our lunch again this year, and again they didn&amp;rsquo;t disappoint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Sponsors: Django Girls 2019</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/call-for-sponsors-django-girls-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/call-for-sponsors-django-girls-2019/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce April 12th - 13th as the official weekend for Django Girls 2019 hosted at The Source. We&amp;rsquo;re now in the process of seeking sponsors to help us put on a successful event!
Sponsorship Overview These slides are also available as a PDF for download.
I Want to Help If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in helping out, please contact the organizers at grandrapids@djangogirls.org. Please check out last year&amp;rsquo;s event to see what our past sponsors have helped us accomplish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyLadies Participates at Holiday Coding Extravaganza</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/2018-12-holiday-coding-extravaganza/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/2018-12-holiday-coding-extravaganza/</guid>
      <description>What is Holiday Coding Extravaganza?  Grand Circus Grand Rapids, The Midwest Tech Project, Loop Coding Center and Start Garden proudly present the Intro to Coding Holiday Extravaganza.
This FREE Intro to Coding Extravangenza is designed for those who are curious about coding, but who have very little or no coding experience.
This event will feature several free workshops and group meetups for adults, plus holiday activities and coding workshops for children including a special visit from a holiday superstar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyLadies Participates at Movies on Monroe</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/07-2018-movies-on-monroe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/07-2018-movies-on-monroe/</guid>
      <description>What is Movies on Monroe?  Movies on Monroe, formerly Movies in the Park, is the premier outdoor film series in Grand Rapids. DGRI and partners present films - free of charge - on a giant video wall along the banks of the Grand River every other Friday from June thru August. Guests are invited to treat the evening like a picnic and bring your own blanket, chairs, beer, wine and snacks for a special night under the stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Girls Grand Rapids 2018 At PyCon</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/2018-djangogirls-pycon/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/2018-djangogirls-pycon/</guid>
      <description>Django Girls GR at PyCon Django Girls Grand Rapids was honored to be asked to manage the Django Girls booth at PyCon in Cleveland, Ohio this year. Because of our participation, we were able to sponsor two volunteers&amp;rsquo; tickets to PyCon that might not otherwise been able to go.
There were three people total that volunteered to help out with the booth. They spent days up to the event preparing, and 3 days at the booth answering questions, inspiring new organizers, and showing PyCon how to have a fun booth.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyLadies GR Represent! Scholarship Announcement</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/scholarship-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/scholarship-2018/</guid>
      <description>PyLadies Grand Rapids is excited to announce Represent!, our Scholarship program, to support and empower people from under-represented groups aspiring to become professional software engineers.
PyLadies We are an international mentorship group with a focus on helping more women become active participants and leaders in the Python open-source community. Our mission is to promote, educate and advance a diverse Python community through outreach, education, conferences, events and social gatherings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyLadies GR Represent! Scholarship Application</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/scholarship-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/scholarship-application/</guid>
      <description>Loading... </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyLadies hosts Django Girls Grand Rapids 2018 Workshop</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/django-girls-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/django-girls-2018/</guid>
      <description>Numbers After a very successful first workshop in 2017, we decided to put on another Django Girls workshop on March 9th - 10th at Start Garden:
 34 attendees 16 sponsors 14 coaches 6 organizers a ton of supportive friends = An Awesome Workshop  Coffee, Code, Repeat Because our workshop from the previous year was such a success we did a lot of the same things for this year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Girls Grand Rapids 2018 Workshop Sponsors</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/2018-sponsors/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/2018-sponsors/</guid>
      <description>Thank you! We are overwhelmed with the generosity of all of our sponsors this year. A shout out to Toptal, Blue Medora, Little Space Studio, Python Software Foundation, Software GR, Stoneburner Video, Zapier, and StickerMule who were all more than happy to step up as sponsors for a second year in a row.
We&amp;rsquo;d also like to thank our new sponsors this year: Jet Brains, Citizen Labs, BoxBoom, Start Garden, and Grand River Bank for joining us for our second annual Django Girls Workshop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Django Girls Grand Rapids 2017 Workshop</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/django-girls-2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/django-girls-2017/</guid>
      <description>Source
Django Girls Grand Rapids First Workshop – Rachell Calhoun – Medium Photo byStoneburner Video Productions
A little back story
Recently having moved to back to the US from Korea and hot on the job search, I was buzzing around all the different tech meetups that I could in my area. The majority that I went to were in Grand Rapids, about an hour away from my hometown. From the first meetup, I started spreading Django and Python love.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>