<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>index on PyLadies Grand Rapids</title>
    <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/categories/index/</link>
    <description>Recent content in index on PyLadies Grand Rapids</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/categories/index/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PyLadies hosts Django Girls Grand Rapids 2019 Workshop</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/2019-05-15-djangogirls-workshop/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/2019-05-15-djangogirls-workshop/</guid>
      <description>Numbers We hosted our third Django Girls workshop on April 12th - 13th at The Source.
 34 attendees 11 sponsors 12 coaches 5 organizers a ton of supportive friends = An Awesome Workshop  Coffee, Code, Repeat Because our workshop from the previous years were such a success we did a lot of the same things for this year. You can read more about that here.
Pita House catered our lunch again this year, and again they didn&amp;rsquo;t disappoint.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Sponsors: Django Girls 2019</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/call-for-sponsors-django-girls-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/call-for-sponsors-django-girls-2019/</guid>
      <description>We&amp;rsquo;re happy to announce April 12th - 13th as the official weekend for Django Girls 2019 hosted at The Source. We&amp;rsquo;re now in the process of seeking sponsors to help us put on a successful event!
Sponsorship Overview These slides are also available as a PDF for download.
I Want to Help If you&amp;rsquo;re interested in helping out, please contact the organizers at grandrapids@djangogirls.org. Please check out last year&amp;rsquo;s event to see what our past sponsors have helped us accomplish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyLadies hosts Django Girls Grand Rapids 2018 Workshop</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/django-girls-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/django-girls-2018/</guid>
      <description>Numbers After a very successful first workshop in 2017, we decided to put on another Django Girls workshop on March 9th - 10th at Start Garden:
 34 attendees 16 sponsors 14 coaches 6 organizers a ton of supportive friends = An Awesome Workshop  Coffee, Code, Repeat Because our workshop from the previous year was such a success we did a lot of the same things for this year.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>