<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>pyladies on PyLadies Grand Rapids</title>
    <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/categories/pyladies/</link>
    <description>Recent content in pyladies on PyLadies Grand Rapids</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/categories/pyladies/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PyLadies Participates at Holiday Coding Extravaganza</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/2018-12-holiday-coding-extravaganza/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/2018-12-holiday-coding-extravaganza/</guid>
      <description>What is Holiday Coding Extravaganza?  Grand Circus Grand Rapids, The Midwest Tech Project, Loop Coding Center and Start Garden proudly present the Intro to Coding Holiday Extravaganza.
This FREE Intro to Coding Extravangenza is designed for those who are curious about coding, but who have very little or no coding experience.
This event will feature several free workshops and group meetups for adults, plus holiday activities and coding workshops for children including a special visit from a holiday superstar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyLadies Participates at Movies on Monroe</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/07-2018-movies-on-monroe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/07-2018-movies-on-monroe/</guid>
      <description>What is Movies on Monroe?  Movies on Monroe, formerly Movies in the Park, is the premier outdoor film series in Grand Rapids. DGRI and partners present films - free of charge - on a giant video wall along the banks of the Grand River every other Friday from June thru August. Guests are invited to treat the evening like a picnic and bring your own blanket, chairs, beer, wine and snacks for a special night under the stars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyLadies GR Represent! Scholarship Announcement</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/scholarship-2018/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/scholarship-2018/</guid>
      <description>PyLadies Grand Rapids is excited to announce Represent!, our Scholarship program, to support and empower people from under-represented groups aspiring to become professional software engineers.
PyLadies We are an international mentorship group with a focus on helping more women become active participants and leaders in the Python open-source community. Our mission is to promote, educate and advance a diverse Python community through outreach, education, conferences, events and social gatherings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>PyLadies GR Represent! Scholarship Application</title>
      <link>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/scholarship-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://grandrapids.pyladies.com/post/scholarship-application/</guid>
      <description>Loading... </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>